espnplayer.com 2010-12-25

# ESPN Player Privacy Policy

**ESPN Player Privacy Policy**

This policy tells you how we collect information from you on the ESPN Player website (the Site), how we protect it and how we use it. ESPN (EUROPE, MIDDLE EAST, AFRICA) LTD ("ESPN"), a company registered in England and Wales with registration number 06565173, controls all personal information which you provide on the Site. ESPN (including its subsidiaries) is a member of the ESPN Group, and is referred to in this Privacy Policy as "we", "us", "our" and "ourselves". 

What type of information we collect about you 

We will collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways including when you register on the Site. We will also notify you at the point of collection when information is being retained and display the relevant Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy explains how we and other companies within the ESPN Group collect, record and use information about you and the choices you can make about how the information is collected and used. The clicking of the "Register" button during your initial registration with our website will indicate your consent to this Privacy Policy. 

What we do with Personally Identifiable information 

We will only pass on your information to third parties in the following situations: 

  * if this was clearly stated at the time of collection or registration and, where required, if you have given permission for this;
  * If we employ another organisation to perform tasks on our behalf - such as hosting the Site. In this case, the organisations may only use your information to fulfil this specific task;
  * If we sell the business of some of the ESPN Group of companies to another organisation or merge with other businesses. In this case, the buyer will only be able to use your information as set out in this Privacy Policy;
  * If we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary for legal proceedings. We may also disclose member information when we believe in good faith that applicable law or regulation requires it.
  * If we use third party processors to administer and process for the purposes notified in the Privacy Policy. We may also share details with third parties (such as auditors or legal advisors) to obtain advice. Any such processing will be governed by an agreement in the form required by law, preserving any statutory data protection rights.

International transfers 

As the ESPN Group operates globally, it may be necessary to transfer your information internationally, and in particular, your information may be transferred to and processed in the United States. The data protection and other laws of other countries, such as the U.S., may not be as comprehensive as those of the European Union. Please be assured that we take all reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. 

Use of Cookies 

We collect information through technology to make our websites more interesting and useful to you. For instance, when you come to one of our websites, we collect your IP address. An IP address is often associated with the portal through which you enter the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our websites. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information. 

Our websites also use cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a website sends to your computer while you are viewing the website. We and other companies use cookies for a variety of purposes. For instance, when you return to one of our websites after logging in, cookies provide information to the website so that the website will remember who you are. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your Web experience smoother, like the features mentioned above, and some of our services will not function properly. 

Our websites use a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, including Web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of websites. We also use these technical methods to analyse the traffic patterns on our websites, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our websites. These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorised by us to collect information on our behalf. We also use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that we send our guests to determine whether our guests have opened those e-mails and/or clicked on links in those e-mails. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable. 

Links to other websites 

You should be aware that when you are on our websites you could be directed to other websites where the personal information collected is outside the control of ESPN. Examples of such websites include the ESPN Soccernet website. 

For example, if you click on a banner advertisement the click may take you off the Site. The privacy policy of the new website will govern the information obtained from you on such website. 

Changes to this policy 

We may change this policy and our terms and conditions from time to time and will post the latest version of the privacy policy on the Site. If we ever wish to use your personal information in a way which is incompatible with the information in this Privacy Policy, we will only do so with your consent. 

Queries 

If you have queries about our use of personal information, you can write to us at ESPN (Europe, Middle East, Africa) Ltd, Business & Legal Affairs Dept, 3 Queen Caroline Street, Hammersmith, London W6 9PE, United Kingdom.
